var questions = [{
    "question": "Which lobe of the brain is responsible for visual information?",
    "option1": "frontal",
    "option2": "temporal",
    "option3": "parietal",
    "option4": "occipital",
    "answer": "occipital"
}, {
    "question": "Which lobe of the brain is repsonsible for making decisions?",
    "option1": "frontal",
    "option2": "temporal",
    "option3": "parietal",
    "option4": "occipital",
    "answer": "frontal"
}, {
    "question": "At what age is the brain fully developed?",
    "option1": "18",
    "option2": "21",
    "option3": "25",
    "option4": "For men, never.",
    "answer": "25"
}, {
    "question": "Which brain region is repsonsible for spatial memeory?",
    "option1": "amygdala",
    "option2": "pre-frontal cortex",
    "option3": "hippocampus",
    "option4": "locus coeruleus",
    "answer": "hippocampus"
}, {
    "question": "Loss of cells in this region results in Parkinson's disease.",
    "option1": "hippocampus",
    "option2": "amygdala",
    "option3": "substantia nigra",
    "option4": "pre-fontal cortex",
    "answer": "substantia nigra"
}, {
    "question": "Lesions of this area result in Urbach-Wiethe (fearless) disease.",
    "option1": "amygdala",
    "option2": "pre-frontal cortex",
    "option3": "hippocampus",
    "option4": "ventral tegmental area",
    "answer": "amygdala"
}, {
    "question": "Which is the last lobe to develop?",
    "option1": "frontal",
    "option2": "temporal",
    "option3": "parietal",
    "option4": "occipital",
    "answer": "frontal"
}, {
    "question": "This brain region is the major relay station for all sensory except smell.",
    "option1": "hypothalamus",
    "option2": "thalamus",
    "option3": "ventral tegmental area",
    "option4": "orbital frontal cortex",
    "answer": "thalamus"
}, {
    "question": "If you suffered a concussion and experience disorganized thoughts and problems with vision, which two lobes were impacted during the injury?",
    "option1": "occipital and temporal lobes",
    "option2": "parietal and frontal lobes",
    "option3": "frontal and temporal lobes",
    "option4": "occipital and frontal lobes",
    "answer": "occipital and frontal lobes"
}, {
    "question": "This brain region is responisble for internal regulation--temperature change, eating, and sleeping.",
    "option1": "hypothalamus",
    "option2": "thalamus",
    "option3": "basolateral amygdala",
    "option4": "septum",
    "answer": "hypthalamus"
}];
